thecoolestguyeverborn.com 2015-11-08

# Privacy Policy | The Coolest Guy Ever Born

It is the Privacy Policy outline which about how we collect information, how we utilize/ use, cookies and web beacons. We http://thecoolestguyeverborn.com/ takes our viewer and visitors privacy importantly.

### **We collect information:**

All websites around web collect information about the basic things like Visitors IP, Geo or Demographic address data, Which browser that the visitor used, Time span of visiting, Time of Visiting on website, reference pages these are some basic information that websites tracked like all we also track those above non-personal identifiable information for maintain purpose only.

### How We Use Visitors Information:

The non identifiable data we collect for maintenance purpose only we do not share these data with Third Party service/ vendors.

Cookies and Web Beacons Information:

We <http://thecoolestguyeverborn.com/> does not use any cookies. This site allows Third party ad company Google to serve advertisement. Google as one of our Third party ad company, it may uses dart cookies on our site also all other site that uses Google ads. Visitors and Users optional to out of uses these dart cookies by visiting Google as and Content Network Privacy Policy page by the following url: http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/.

All those mention Information about above Google uses dart cookies is Subject to Google own privacy policy. For more description or information You may follow above link for more details.

#### Note Please:

We http;//thecoolestguyeverborn.com/ have no control or access over these Third party advertisers or companies cookies. These Third party advertisers or companies may use non-personal identifiable information for server better ads. For disabling or enabling cookies please contact to the Third party advertisers or companies.

Please [Contact](http://thecoolestguyeverborn.com/contact-us/) any time for any Privacy Policy related Information.
